Dude, I'm fired up to be here. Having a
good week, dude. Just getting pumped on
civil service.
Hey, I got summoned for jury duty.
>> Yeah, felt nice to be summoned.
[laughter]
Got a letter from the court. They're
like, "We summon you." And I was like,
"I'm there."
I was pumped. I was ready to jur it up,
you know? I had a cardigan. I had
non-prescription glasses. I was like,
"Let's decide this case.
So, I get there. I'm in the waiting
room. I'm waiting all day. At the end of
the day, they're like, "Okay,
you can go." [laughter]
They even consider me.
I'm like, "You summon me and you don't
even take the time for consideration."
[laughter]
And not to be braggy, but I'm a lawyer's
wet dream. Okay? [laughter]
You can convince me of anything.
I'm a Scientologist
[cheering]
[laughter]
>> and a Mormon.
Yeah, [laughter]
that's true, dude.
Yeah, my entire cupboard is filled with
Herbal Life
[laughter]
and Koku. Oh, my dog right here. Dude,
are you Scientologist? [laughter]
I don't know.
>> Oh, hell yeah, dude. I was watching the
OJ documentary. As soon as he's trying
to put the glove on, I was like, "Oh my
god, he's innocent." [laughter]
That's what he could have had. Judicial
system,
>> but you don't want me. I don't want you.
So, whatever.
[laughter]
I I'm going to see my family soon. Going
to see my dad.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Utah.
My dad's the best. He's just he's
intense, you know? He's always asking me
questions I don't know the answer to.
He's always like, "Hey, what's the
average price of a house
in this neighborhood?" I'm like, "Dad,
I'm not Warren Buffet." Okay. [laughter]
I don't know the answers
to these questions, but he's always on
my case. He's like, "Who's the
president?" I'm like, I don't [\h__\h]
[laughter]
Sometimes he's like, "Do you even know
anything?" I'm like, "Well, actually, I
know nothing." [laughter]
That's the Socratic paradox.
[laughter]
He's like, "What are you, an asshole?"
"Actually, I'm a philosophy major."
Yeah, thank you for the tuition.
[laughter]
A lot of people bag on philosophy majors
like, "You guys can't do anything. What
do you guys do? can't do anything. I'm
like, "Oh, you mean besides enlighten
people,
inspire wisdom, courage, virtue?" "Yeah,
sorry about that." [laughter]
They're like, "Yeah, well, you can't do
anything in the real world." I'm like,
"Oh, you think the world's real?"
[laughter and clears throat]
"Yeah, [laughter]
clearly you haven't read Kong." All
right.
Stupid con. [laughter]
My dad's a doctor. not to flex.
He's a doctor. Naturally, I rebelled and
I went holistic.
[laughter]
He's always trying to push big farm on
me non-stop.
One time I was surfing. I cut my foot on
the reef. He's like, "You need neoporn
for that." And I was like, "Nice try,
Chief.
[laughter]
I already pissed on it.
Can't listen to anything he says.
Everything he says is sponsored by
Fizer. [laughter]
One time I had a headache. He's like,
"Why don't you take some al leave?" I'm
like, "Okay, Fouchy.
[laughter]
>> How about I hop in the ice bath, boost
my mitochondria?"
[laughter]
>> Yeah, that's the powerhouse of the cell.
[cheering]
>> Orange County, you love [laughter]
you love holistic science. I'm done.
[laughter]
But yeah, I don't trust doctors, okay? I
trust tan jack dudes. [laughter]
Think I'm going to trust some Harvard
dough boy? Get the hell out of here. I
trust the guy in a speedo doing chi gong
on the beach. [laughter]
Like, oh, you think it's the flu? Cuz my
health guru Troy thinks it's 5G.
[laughter]
Troy's ball slapping. Yeah, it's 5G.
It's totally 5G. Oh yeah, dude.
>> Yeah. Every time I go to the doctor, I'm
like, "Take your shirt off. You have a
six-pack. You're not working on me."
Okay. I'll go see Troy. I know where he
is. He slack lines on Tuesdays.
[laughter]
Not only is Troy my health guru, he's
also my shaman and my landlord.
[laughter]
He's my spiritual master from the Far
East, aka Tampa. [laughter]
Troy's got me into every diet. You know,
I've done vegan, keto, solar.
It's tough in the winter. [laughter]
Sat there like,
"Fuck, I'm hungry."
[laughter]
Most recently, he got me into carnivore.
Have you guys heard about this?
>> You just eat meat all the time.
>> He's like, "Brother, you got to try it."
I've been eating steaks non-stop. I
haven't been depressed once.
My boner is next level. [laughter]
I was like, dude, that's a great pitch.
I'm in. [laughter]
I was like, so what do I do? He's like,
you just eat ribe eyes all day. I was
like, done deal. So, I had my first day
of carnivore. I was just crushing ribe
eyes. By the end of the first day, I was
like, whoa, this is way outside my
budge.
[laughter]
the carnivore diet. They should call it
the rich man's diet. [laughter]
So, I had to resort to In-N-Out
McDonald's patties and I was just cr
Yeah, I was just crushing McDonald's
patties. After about 6 months, my
buddies were like, "Dude, how do you
feel?" I'm like, "Dude, I've had
diarrhea this whole time."
[laughter]
They're like, "Isn't that bad?" I'm
like, "Troy says I'm detoxing." And
[laughter]
I've had so many vegetables. I need to
clear them out with the meal. [laughter]
Actually, we should be having diarrhea
all the time.
It's something they don't want you to
know.
[laughter]
Uh, I got engaged last year.
>> Yeah. [cheering]
Yeah. We met the oldfashioned way, you
know, to rave.
Saw behind the DJ booth. I was on Molly.
[laughter]
Walked up to her and I was like, "Hey,
do you want to make out?" She's like,
"Yeah."
Then I started giving her a light show.
Just [laughter]
just gloving the [\h__\h] out of her. Just
she was just screaming from her dome
just oh
won't get it.
Oh. Oh.
[laughter]
Then the beat dropped. I was like
I was like I'll DM you later.
We get sush. [laughter]
She's the best. We We rarely fight. Uh
biggest fight we got into is about a
year ago. She's like, "Hey, do you want
to come shred Aspen?" I was like, "Uh,
for sure." She's like, "Cool. What board
do you ride, Burton?" I was
[clears throat] like, "Actually, it's
plural."
She's like, "What? I ride two twigs."
You what? I ski. [laughter]
Then there was a long silence. And she's
like, "So, you're gay?"
I'm like, "I'm not gay. I just ski. I
went to boarding school. It's very
snoody." [laughter]
She's like, "But you surf. Why would you
not snowboard?" I'm like, "Cuz father
wouldn't allow it." [laughter]
Said it was very uncou.
Said snowboarders, they just push snow
all over the mountain. He's like,
"They're savages." [laughter] And I
brought up to one time I WAS LIKE,
"PAPA,
>> [laughter]
>> CAN I try snowboarding? He's like, if
you go snowboarding, you cannot have
fondue at operate ski. I was like, okay,
Jesus. [laughter]
So, I told him, I'm like, look, babe, I
brought it up to papa, but he said, no,
fondue. My hands are tied, babe. You
understand?
But now she doesn't trust me with guys.
[laughter]
Cuz I like to do mogul, you know? I
hit a jump, I do the twist move.
>> [laughter]
>> She's like, "What was that?" I'm like,
"It's actually a really respected move.
[laughter]
Johnny Mosley did in the '9s."
>> Yeah.
Yeah. Now she doesn't trust me with
guys. Like a couple weekends ago, it was
a Sunday. My fiance is like, "What are
you doing today?" I'm like, "I'm gonna
go hiking with my buddy Frank." She's
like, "You're going hiking with a guy?"
I'm [laughter] like, "Yeah, he wants to
go hiking." like, "What's the ish?"
[laughter]
She's like, "Well, is he going to try to
hook up with you?"
[laughter]
I was like, "I don't think so."
She's like, "Well, guys, guys want to
hook up with you." I was like, "Well,
what about chicks?" [laughter]
She's like, "I don't worry about that.
[laughter]
He's
like, "But I'm not gay." Like, "Yeah,
but you're just so sweet." [laughter]
I'm like, "You think I'm so sweet I just
let some guy [\h__\h] me?"
[laughter]
What's that, Frank? Oh, you want to have
your away with me?
>> Yeah, no worries.
All right, that's my time, everyone.
Thank you so much.
>> [music]